http://www.pts.edu/privacy

Alumnae/iCalendarWebmailMYPTS
AboutAboutPresident's WelcomeSeminary FactsHistoryPTS Out and AboutDirectoryStaffBoard of DirectorsWorshipLocation and DirectionsCampus SafetyInstitutional EffectivenessEmployment OpportunitiesMissionParticipating in God's ongoing mission in the world, Pittsburgh Theological Seminary is a community of Christ joining in the Spirit's work of forming and equipping people for ministries familiar and yet to unfold and communities present and yet to be gathered.
AdmissionsHow to ApplyFinancial AidTuition and FeesVisit CampusCampus VideosExperience Virtual ClassPittsburgh and the RegionStudent HousingPeople of PTSContact AdmissionsIn the Way of JesusSince 1794 Pittsburgh Theological Seminary has been preparing students in the way of Jesus. We welcome neighbors; share meals, differences, and experiences; expand our minds; and expect to be challenged by the broad range of beliefs we bring to the table.
AcademicsMaster's DegreesDoctor of Ministry DegreeCertificate ProgramsNon-Degree StudentsAuditing a CourseFacultySeminary on Your ScheduleField EducationAcademic CalendarStudent HandbookRegistrarCourse CatalogCourse DescriptionsAcademic RigorThe established academic rigor of more than 200 years of theological education, and the depth and diversity of our faculty, ensure our student community learns, grows, and flourishes on a path to practical ministry. Our students prepare to engage in God's work with parishes, nonprofits, and institutions specific to their call.
ResourcesBarbour LibraryAdvent Devotional 2020Digital DownloadsPublicationsWriting CenterChurch Planting InitiativeContinuing EducationKelso MuseumZeitah ExcavationsMetro-Urban InstituteMiller Summer Youth InstituteWorld Mission InitiativeService to the Church and CommunityFrom our extensive theological library, archaeological museum, and printed and digital publications, to welcoming participation in our robust continuing education program, mission-related opportunities, and youth ministry institute, the Seminary models what it means to be a valuable resource for the church and the world.
GiveDonate OnlineCrowdfunding for Special ProjectsWays to Make Your GiftGifts in Honor or MemoryPlanned GivingAdvancement StaffSupport Theological EducationWhen you give to Pittsburgh Seminary, you invest in men and women who, in and out of the classroom, are preparing to participate with Christ in the transformative work of gospel ministry around the globe—whether in traditional church settings, entrepreneurial church plants, or missional initiatives. Your giving supports student scholarships, faculty development, educational programs such as the World Mission Initiative, Church Planting Initiative, and Metro-Urban Institute, and much more.
Alumnae/iCalendarWebmailMYPTS
Say Hello
Submit
Say Hello
Internet Privacy Policy
Apply Online Now
Request Info
Visit the Campus
Collecting and Using Personal Information
When you visit our sites and when you communicate with us via our sites, we will not collect personal information about you, unless you provide it voluntarily. Pittsburgh Theological Seminary (PTS) will not sell, license, transmit, or disclose this information outside of PTS unless (a) expressly authorized by you, (b) necessary to enable PTS contractors or agents to perform certain functions for us, or (c) required or permitted by law. In all cases, we will disclose the information consistent with applicable laws and regulations and we will require the recipient to protect the information and use it only for the purpose it was provided.
E-Mail
Please note that your e-mail may be viewed by others while in transit to us. For that reason, you should not use e-mail to communicate information that is confidential. If you wish, you may contact us instead via my.pts.edu, telephone at the numbers provided at various locations on our sites, or fax.
Other Information / Cookies
You should also be aware that when you visit our websites, we collect certain information that does not identify you personally, but provides us with “usage data,” such as the number of visitors we receive or what pages are visited most often. This data helps us to analyze and improve the usefulness of the information we provide at these websites.
Linking to Other Sites
PTS websites link to other websites, not owned or controlled by PTS. PTS is not responsible for the privacy practices used by other websites or their content or accuracy. Links to non-PTS websites do not constitute or imply endorsement by PTS.
Security
PTS follows best practice security standards designed to protect non-public personal information.
Changes to This Statement
PTS may change this policy from time to time. This policy is not intended to and does not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.
Pittsburgh Theological Seminary
616 North Highland Avenue | Pittsburgh, PA 15206
Phone: 412-362-5610
Contact Us
Directions
Employment
Privacy Policy
